<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Circle related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_circle">Grey Cells</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_circle_advertising">A simple experiment that aims to stimulate your grey matter through grey circles.</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_circle_explanation">Touch one circle to pop them into four smaller ones until the shape of the image is visible.</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_circle_hints">
        <item>Earthling, welcome to our first experiment. To stimulate your cells, split circles as Mose split the water. However, don\'t split them in two halves but in four parts. Hopefully at some point the stimulation of your cells is enough and you can see a picture due to the better shapes. If not, I have to continue the test series with our Parameciums. They mastered the tests with flying colours.</item>
        <item>Demo version finished. Get the full version for only 39,99€! Just kidding. Nevertheless, have a quick look in the shop. There are many handy items. For example the intergalactic Circlelaser-Turbo-Cutter…And by the way, you should always pick up your reward in the achievement menu!</item>
        <item>You can find a quick guide at the top right corner. You can skip a picture, if you don\'t see the solution.</item>
        <item>If you want more pictures from WiseMind, you can get new ones via download in the shop!</item>
        <item>Later, if this experiment is successful, you can choose between different experiment types in the middle of game. Or you can continue all skipped experiments.</item>
        <item>Sometimes human eyes recognize some pictures from a certain distance. Sometimes a screenshot is helping, too.</item>
        <item>Did you notice that WiseMind\'s compliment appears green sometimes? In that case, you finished the experiment better or faster as usually expected.</item>
        <item>You get daily bonus neurons for the first couple of solved experiments. The bonus is
            decreasing shortly and depends on the difficulty and length of the experiment type.</item>
        <item>More exclamation marks mean a higher bonus.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="article_circle_divide_by_move_feature_name">Intergalactic Circlelaser-Turbo-Cutter</string>
    <string name="article_circle_divide_by_move_feature_descr">Divide circles by moving the finger. Very relaxing!</string>

    <!-- Snow related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_snow">Angry Cell</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_snow_advertising">A more complex experiment where you guide an angry cell through the foggy parts of your mind and collect strange things.</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_snow_explanation">Move the cell to your finger or, later, by tilting the device. Collect candies, grow bigger, don\'t touch walls and EXPLODE.</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_snow_hints">
        <item>A new test. We place some contaminated biological material of another species close to your cell to test your cell\'s reaction. Pay attention to the particles which are emitted from the material. They will damage your cell. As in policy we will do our best to obscure everything else with a lie </item>
        <item>We hope to gain a better insight into the earthly grey matter which is part of your central nervous system. We had to remove a cell from your brain. Don\'t worry, drinking alcohol kills far more cells.?</item>
        <item>Angeli is like the Truth serum ScitiLop and shows harsh reality to the cell. We tried to give that stuff to a politician but the cell exploded instantly. That was a mess!</item>
        <item>Angeli has three cognitive states. The first one will protect you completely against particles or wall collisions. Toxic candies will decrease that effect.</item>
        <item>The second cognitive state has less protection against particles or wall collisions. Angeli will be dizzy in the third state and does not protect you.</item>
        <item>You can push Angeli out of the control area. It won\'t bother you anymore, but collecting candies get more risky.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="article_snow_feature_orientation_sensor_name">Balancing act</string>
    <string name="article_snow_feature_orientation_sensor_descr">Enables choosing to control the cell by tilting the phone!</string>
    <string name="article_snow_feature_orientation_sensor_on">Tilting</string>
    <string name="article_snow_feature_orientation_sensor_off">Pressing</string>

    <string-array name="devil_talk_recovering_start">
        <item>My stomach hurts…</item>
        <item>Outch</item>
        <item>Need… to pro…tect</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="devil_talk_recovered">
        <item>I\'m fine again!</item>
        <item>I had an upset stomach!</item>
        <item>I did this just for you!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="devil_talk_return">
        <item>I\'m back!</item>
        <item>Did you miss me?</item>
        <item>I will never leave you!</item>
        <item>Resurrection in 3…2… nevermind, I\'m already back.</item>
        <item>Overly attached? I call it passion.</item>
        <item>Like the moon will not leave the earth, I will not leave you!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="devil_talk_killed">
        <item>I\'ll be back.</item>
        <item>Noooooooo…</item>
        <item>What are you doing?</item>
        <item>Staaap!</item>
        <item>Let me love youuu!</item>
        <item>You need me!</item>
        <item>The candy is a lie!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="devil_talk_cell_eat_candy">
        <item>Nooooo, that\'s poison</item>
        <item>Don\'t you see it\'s not candy?!</item>
        <item>Why you do this, stap</item>
        <item>Stop…eating candy.</item>
        <item>Sigh…</item>
        <item>Stop or you will get fat!</item>
        <item>No toothbrush, no candy</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="devil_talk_cell_eat_candy_explosive">
        <item>Wooo, keep calm, keeeeeep calm</item>
        <item>Remember the last time you were happy?</item>
        <item>Fast, kiss the wall</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="devil_talk_mock">
        <item>Nevermind me, I\'m just spinning around</item>
        <item>Why don\'t you love me back?</item>
        <item>I just want to help</item>
        <item>Tickling me won\'t do anything</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Triangle related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_triangle">Triluminati</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_triangle_advertising">A simple experiment. Your grey cells have gained some colour and the experiment some edges.</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_triangle_explanation">Press inside a triangle to split it in two smaller ones. You will recognise the hidden image soon.</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_triangle_hints">
        <item>WiseMind says that I\'m talking too much. Do you think that too? Well, I will keep it short: A colourful counterpart of the circle test. Hit a triangle to split it in two smaller ones. Why do we need this? To test your colour vision.</item>
        <item>If you touch multiple triangles at their ends you will split them all. Magic! Otherwise everything is like the Circle experiment.</item>
        <item>I\'m a respected scientist. If you ask such easy things I could react annoyed…</item>
        <item>If you want to waste your short life time by pushing useless buttons, be my guest.</item>
        <item>Are you in love with me or why can\'t you just stop?!</item>
        <item>OK earth being, now I have enough! One glass of the predator drug should be enough to knock out an elephant. Bye bye!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="article_triangle_divide_by_move_feature_name">Intergalactic Turbolaser-Triangle-Cutter</string>
    <string name="article_triangle_divide_by_move_feature_descr">Dr. Drams has tortured his employees for almost a month to upgrade the Circlelaser for you!</string>

    <!-- Dice related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_dice">Alien-Cube</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_dice_advertising">A tricky and complicated experiment for the patients and logistician. You need to move dices on a grid and combine them.</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_dice_explanation">Touch an empty field to create dices with different number of points. Move and combine dices with equal numbers to reveal the image.</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_dice_hints">
        <item>A very complicated test. Create new dices by touching empty fields. Combine dices
            with the same number and colour to get more transparency in the shown areas. There
            are three basic dices red, yellow and green. And there is the special Alien-Cube. The
            Alien-Cube has special effects on each basic dice.</item>
        <item>We have to do this complicated experiment as we discovered a strange anomaly: Somehow your earthly cubes miss one dimension. By mistake there are only six cube faces instead of nine. Of course we have to test your brain on reality in terms of combination, numbers, tactic, logistics, colour, movement, logic and speed. Ay, I think it\'s a mistake, too. I told WiseMind we are expecting too much, but I have to execute this command.</item>
        <item>Something you need to know about the Alien-Cube: Alien-Cube on red results in a green dice with the same number. Plus some transparency in the shown areas!</item>
        <item>Alien-Cube on yellow will reveal the field completely but both cubes will vanish!</item>
        <item>Alien-Cube on green results in purple. This is a special dice as the revealed fields are mobile but depends on the number of points!</item>
        <item>My suggestion? If you already got a green dice, combine the Alien-Cube with a red one. You get a green one immediately plus some transparency for free.\nIf you want to gamble, try the yellow one. Maybe one field is enough to see the solution!\nIf you want to \"scan\" the whole picture, take a green dice.</item>
        <item>If I combine the Alien-Cube on a green dice, usually on a 4, 5 or 6. Why? Well, the proportion fields:transparency is the best one in my opinion.</item>
        <item>Maybe the grid is full, but that\'s not a tragedy. You may lose red and yellow dices and some transparency but you get some free space again.</item>
        <item>Like a wormhole you can move red and yellow dices in jumps as long as there is a path. Do you think you can jump into the hyperspace when jumping over the longest distance?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="article_dice_improved_start_name">Improved start</string>
    <string name="article_dice_improved_start_descr">A higher dice is available when
        starting the riddle.</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_dice_article_improved_start_products">
        <item>Starts with a yellow dice instead.</item>
        <item>Starts with a green dice instead.</item>
        <item>Starts with an alien dice instead.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Jumper related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_jumper">Monstarathon</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_jumper_advertising">A moving experiment. You jump and run and need
        to avoid colliding with obstacles!</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_jumper_explanation">Touch to jump or keep pressed to doublejump
        over obstacles. Ideas will slowly reveal the forgotten image</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_jumper_hints">
        <item>Humans are strange creatures. A donkey is moving if you keep a carrot in front of
            his head, for Homo sapiens it requires a bundle of money, even tough you can\'t even eat
            it.</item>
        <item>Whatever. We run some tests on a business men and had to block his memory. Luckily, you can break
            the blockades by jumping over different obstacles. It was easy to motivate the business man for a marathon with a simple thought: \"At the end of the rainbow you will be rewarded by a pot of money!\" What a pity, that there is no rainbow in the middle of the night.</item>
        <item>Click once: Jump, Click twice: Double Jump. Got it?</item>
        <item>You will pass different stages. Depending on the difficulty more memory will come back
            .</item>
        <item>Our Business Man will remember something every x-passed obstacles. But not every
            idea will be relevant for the forgotten picture.</item>
        <item>Practice makes perfect. But some people are just not made for Jump and Runs.</item>
        <item>You wonder who is Manomnom? A mysterious being!</item>
        <item>Manomnom is waiting for you in the last area. As my master loves him so much, you
            will meet him at the end of each stage.</item>
        <item>You should\'t touch Manomnom. But his laser is just a show. A show with great style,
            don\'t you think so?</item>
        <item>You wonder why he wants to laser everything? Unfortunately he got crazy after eating a Magnetar.</item>
        <item>Manomnom and I, we are the sweeties of our Master!</item>
        <item>Oh Manomno, you silly ninny, why did you eat the Magnetar… Just why?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="riddle_jumper_collision_break">
        <item>You can do better</item>
        <item>Here we go again</item>
        <item>You can make it further</item>
        <item>Game Over!?!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="riddle_jumper_new_highscore">New record %1$dm</string>
    <string name="riddle_jumper_old_highscore">Current record %1$dm</string>
    <string name="article_jumper_start_further_name">Triple XxX</string>
    <string name="article_jumper_start_further_descr">Start from 200m instead of walking through the easy part.</string>
    <string name="article_jumper_better_ideas_name">Better ideas</string>
    <string name="article_jumper_better_ideas_descr">Greatly improves the chance that ideas will
        clear the clouded mind.</string>

    <!-- Memory related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_memory">Memory</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_memory_advertising">For some it\'s a simple experiment. For most, mostly adults, it\'s somehow difficult. You need to remember cards!</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_memory_explanation">Find a matching pair of cards by clicking on a card and remembering its picture!</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_memory_hints">
        <item>This time we want to answer the following question: \"How catastrophic is the earthly brain regarding memories?\" We gonna find a solution with this experiment. We keep the instruction as simple as possible, especially for you: Find matching pairs of cards! You have to remember them on your own.</item>
        <item>When finding a matching pair, a path will reveal all cards between the cards for a short time.</item>
        <item>The path reverses everything: red cards become yellow, and yellow become green again.</item>
        <item>Different card colours may help you remember a picture\'s position. And only one grey
            card can be visible at a time.</item>
        <item>No one and nothing can stop you to grab a pen and a piece of paper to make some notes or to take a screenshot. Except your pride. The secret service will see that you can\'t remember a pair of cards. Even little human beings and some animals can do that without any help!</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- Developer related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_developer">Developer</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_developer_advertising" translatable="false">COOOL?!</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_developer_explanation">Hi self or brother.</string>

    <!-- Torchlight related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_torchlight">Torchlight</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_torchlight_advertising" translatable="false">COOOL?!</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_torchlight_explanation">Something happens later</string>

    <!-- Flow related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_flow">Cellflow</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_flow_advertising">An oasis of chaos for slobs. Put down Cellis in
        the unknown chaos to discover known points and shapes of the image! A simple experiment!</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_flow_explanation">Click anywhere in the field to create cellflows.
        If Cellis hit an edge of the image, they follow the shapes of the picture.</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_flow_hints">
        <item>Maybe you think this is a confusing experiment, on the whole that\'s how to
            describe your mind: Confused and empty. At least at the beginning! We recreated your
            mind with a model.\nClick anywhere on the field to place some Cellis. If Cellis hit
            an edge of the image, they will follow them and reveal the picture at the same
            time!</item>
        <item>Not every Celli is a specialized and intelligent cell. Only every third Celli will
            detect edges.</item>
        <item>Celli\'s maximum lifetime is always the same.</item>
        <item>However not every Celli will work until the end. Most of them collide in a dead end.</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- Lazor related -->
    <string name="riddle_type_lazor">Lazor</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_lazor_advertising">An arcade experiment with some futuristic
        aspects. Defend your city against descending comets in an arcade point-and-click shooter
        .</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_lazor_explanation">The closest charged Lazor is firing towards
        clicked point and will explode there or on collision. Stop the comets!</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_lazor_hints">
        <item>A simulation to test your reaction to extraterrestrial threats. Use the lazors to shoot on incoming comets which threat your city. On collision or when reaching the clicked point the lazor explodes. Along its tail the corresponding colour gets visible.</item>
        <item>Pay attention to the canons plants to see, when the lazor gets ready to shoot. By the way, always the next canon plant fires as long as it\'s ready to shoot of course.</item>
        <item>Depending on the costs of the next hint, you can eventually see if it\'s a useful
            hint. Nevertheless it\'s possible that you already know the fact and you spent the
            neurons, your money, for nothing.</item>
        <item>White comets cover and uncover the path completely. Shoot them first by any cost!</item>
        <item>Hitting a comet later increases the revealed area and the risk to miss a comet! Later, if comets are spawning much faster, you should try to hit them as early as possible as you won\'t be able to stop them all!</item>
        <item>In some situations you won\'t be able to prevent an impact. Decide as fast as possible, which comet will strike your city and try to stop the other ones.</item>
        <item>The green shield protects your city against any impacts. Especially the white
            comets\' negative influence is decreased.</item>
        <item>A covered eye in the achievement menu means a hidden achievement. Either you get a hint or you will find it by chance.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="riddle_type_lazor_article_protection_at_name">Reactor improvements</string>
    <string name="riddle_type_lazor_article_protection_at_descr">The protective barrier requires less energy in the future.</string>
    <string-array name="riddle_type_lazor_article_protection_at_products">
        <item>Protects if reactor reached 40%.</item>
        <item>Protects if reactor reached 30%</item>
        <item>Protects if reactor reached 25%</item>
        <item>Protects if reactor reached 20%. If the shield is active, 3% more white comets will
            spawn.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>